0,0,0,,Coming in
Coming in
0,0,0,,Coming out
Coming out
0,0,0,,mawari mite mi na
周り　見てみな
0,0,0,,noizu mamire de
ノイズ　まみれで
0,0,0,,You can't see me but you hear me loud
You can't see me but you hear me loud
0,0,0,,Don't that make you crazy now
Don't that make you crazy now
0,0,0,,me wo korase kono sekai wa
目を凝らせ　この世界は
0,0,0,,It's all upside down
It's all upside down
0,0,0,,Don't stop modorenai Flashback
Don't stop　戻れない　Flashback
0,0,0,,Look up kidzukeba It's all past
Look up　気づけば　It's all past
0,0,0,,Too fast hikisakaresou sa Ah ah…
Too fast　引き裂かれそうさ　Ah ah...
0,0,0,,Don't stop modorenai Flashback
Don't stop　戻れない　Flashback
0,0,0,,Look up kidzukeba It's all past
Look up　気づけば　It's all past
0,0,0,,Too fast hikisakaresou sa Ah ah…
Too fast　引き裂かれそうさ　Ah ah...
0,0,0,,Don't stop modorenai Flashback
Don't stop　戻れない　Flashback
0,0,0,,Look up kidzukeba It's all past
Look up　気づけば　It's all past
0,0,0,,Too fast hikisakaresou sa Ah ah…
Too fast　引き裂かれそうさ　Ah ah...
0,0,0,,Don't stop modorenai Flashback
Don't stop　戻れない　Flashback
0,0,0,,Flashback
Flashback